<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<applicationDocs targetNamespace="http://wadl.dev.java.net/2009/02">

    <doc xml:lang="en" title="Groundwork Foundation Rest API">
        <h3>Groundwork Foundation Rest API Metadata</h3>
        <p>
            The Groundwork Foundation REST API for performing query and administrative operations
            on monitored entities in the Groundwork enterprise foundation server.
        </p>
        <p>
            Operations supported are of the categories:
            <ul>
                <li>lookup operations - lookup entities by their primary key host name</li>
                <li>list operations - list all entities in the system, with optional depth and paging parameters</li>
                <li>query operations - query for entities using an object query language with optional depth and paging parameters</li>
                <li>post operations - administrative batch operations to add or update entities. Works with lists of one or more entities</li>
                <li>delete operations - administrative batch operations to delete entities. Works with lists of one or more entities</li>
            </ul>
        </p>
        <p>
            Note that post and delete operations are not transactional. If a list of 10 entities are passed in to be added, and
            if, for example, two entities fail to update, the other eight entities will still be persisted. The results for all
            post and delete operations return the same DtoOperationResults list of DtoOperationResult (see XML schema), holding
            the result (success, failure, warning) of each sub-operation.
        </p>
        The Rest API supports retrieval operations (lookup,list,query) of up to three depths, depending on the particular API:
        <ul>
            <li>shallow - return all attributes and properties</li>
            <li>deep - returns all shallow attributes and properties, plus all associated elements and lists of elements at shallow depth</li>
            <li>simple - names and descriptions only</li>
        </ul>
    </doc>

</applicationDocs>
