<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="com.icesoft.ide.eclipse.icefaces.facelets.feature"
      label="ICEfaces facelets Eclipse tooling"
      version="3.5.2.200904081303"
      provider-name="ICEsoft Technologies, Inc."
      plugin="com.icesoft.ide.eclipse.icefaces.facelets.core"
      colocation-affinity="org.eclipse.jst.jsf.facelet.feature">

   <description url="http://www.icefaces.org">
      ICEfaces integration with Eclipse v3.4.
   </description>

   <copyright url="http://www.icesoft.com/downloads/license_community.html">
      Copyright (c) 2007 ICEsoft Technologies, Inc. All rights reserved. This program and the accompanying materials are made available under the terms of the ICEsoft Community Edition license which accompanies this distribution, and is available at http://www.icesoft.com/downloads/license_community.html\n\
Copyright (c) 2008 Oracle Corporation.\
All rights reserved. This program and the accompanying materials\
are made available under the terms of the Eclipse Public License v1.0\
which accompanies this distribution, and is available at\
http://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-v10.html\
\n\
Contributors:\n\
    Oracle Corporation - initial API and implementation\n
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://www.icesoft.com/downloads/license_community.html">
      COMMUNITY LICENSE AGREEMENT

By downloading software of ICEsoft Technologies, Inc. or its subsidiaries (&quot;ICEsoft&quot;) from this site, you agree to the following terms and conditions. If you do not agree with such terms and conditions, do not download the software. The terms of an end user license agreement accompanying a particular software file upon installation or download of the software shall supersede the terms presented below.

1. THIS LICENSE AGREEMENT (&quot;Agreement&quot;) is made and entered into as of the download date between ICESOFT TECHNOLOGIES,INC.
a Delaware corporation having a principal place of business at 20555 N. Pima Road, Suite 100, Scottsdale, AZ 85255 
(&quot;ICEsoft&quot;), and the individual and organization downloading the evaluation software (&quot;User&quot;). The parties agree as follows:
2. DEVELOPMENT LICENSE GRANT:  Subject to the terms and conditions of this Agreement, ICEsoft hereby grants to User a restricted, non-transferable, non-exclusive, object code development license: (i) to use and modify the Licensed Software;
and (ii) to reproduce the Licensed Software for archive purposes, consistent with User&apos;s standard archive procedures.
3. DEPLOYMENT LICENSE GRANT:  Subject to the terms and conditions of this Agreement, ICEsoft grants to User a non-exclusive,non-transferable, royalty free license: (i) to reproduce copies of the Licensed Software, solely in Object Code; and (ii) to 
distribute such copies to Third Party Users worldwide, through multiple tiers of distribution, solely as inseparably embedded content within the User&apos;s application. 
4. RESTRICTIONS: Except as expressly permitted by this Agreement, User may not: (i) translate, reverse engineer, de-compile, disassemble or attempt to derive the Source Code of the Licensed Software provided to User in Object Code; (ii) sublicense, rent, lease, loan, timeshare, sell, distribute, disclose, publish, assign, or transfer any rights in or grant a security interest in the  Licensed Software.
5. SUPPORT AND MAINTENANCE:  ICEsoft shall bear no obligation to support or maintain the Licensed Software. Any support provided shall be at the sole discretion of ICEsoft.
6. OWNERSHIP:  User shall not have any obligation to provide or disclose to ICEsoft any modifications made to the Licensed Software.  Notwithstanding the foregoing, ICEsoft and its licensors shall retain exclusive ownership of all worldwide Intellectual Property Rights in and to the Licensed Software. User hereby assigns to ICEsoft all Intellectual Property Rights it may have or obtain in and to any modifications to the Licensed Software. All rights in and to the Licensed Software not expressly granted to User in this Agreement are reserved by ICEsoft and its licensors.
7. TRADEMARKS:  This License does not grant permission to use the trade name, trademarks, service marks or product names of ICEsoft, except as required for reasonable and customary used in describing the origin of the work. Any and all
copyrights located in the License Software shall be reproduced in any reshipment of the code.
8. NONCOMPETE: User shall not develop nor make available any work product derived from the Licensed Software, any solution that shall compete with ICEsoft&apos;s ICEfaces product. Licensed Software may not be resold or redistributed on a stand alone basis. 
9. TERMINATION: ICEsoft shall have the right to terminate this Agreement if the User is in material breach of any term or condition of this Agreement and fails to remedy such breach within thirty (30) days after receipt of written notice of such breach. Upon material breach or termination of the agreement all rights granted in this agreement shall be revoked.
10. DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY:  The software is licensed on an &quot;AS IS&quot; BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTESS OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either expressed or implied, including and without limitation any warranties or conditions of TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT,
MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. The User shall assume any and all risk associated with development of the Licensed   Software and its Subsequent redistribution.
11. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY: ICESOFT AND ITS LICENSORS SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL
OR INDIRECT DAMAGES OF ANY KIND (INCLUDING DAMAGES FOR INTERRUPTION OF BUSINESS, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS, LOSS OF PROFITS, OR THE LIKE).
12. GENERAL: Customer shall not export or re-export the Software in violation of the export control laws of the United States and/or any other jurisdiction. This Agreement will be governed in all respects by the laws of the State of Delaware without regard to conflicts of law principles as applied to contracts entered into between residents thereof and performed entirely within the State. All disputes arising under this Agreement shall be brought in Superior Court of the State of Delaware. If any legal action or proceeding is brought for the enforcement of this Agreement, or because 
of any alleged dispute, breach, default or misrepresentation in connection with any of the provisions of this Agreement, the successful or prevailing party or parties shall be entitled to recovery reasonable attorneys&apos; fees and other costs incurred in that action or proceeding, in addition to any other relief to which such party may be entitled. If any provision or provisions of this Agreement are determined to be invalid, illegal or unenforceable, the validity, legality and enforceability of the remaining provisions of this Agreement will not in any way be affected or impaired thereby. This Agreement may not be assigned, sublicensed, or otherwise transferred by Customer without ICEsoft&apos;s prior written consent. Nothing contained herein shall be construed as creating any agency, employment relationship, partnership, principal-agent or other form  of joint enterprise between the parties. This Agreement constitutes the complete, final and exclusive statement of the agreement between ICEsoft and Customer, which supersedes all proposals, oral or written, and all other 
communications between the parties relating to the subject matter of this Agreement. No waiver, alteration or modification of the provisions of this Agreement will be valid unless made in writing and signed by a corporate officer of ICEsoft. Each party agrees that use of pre-printed forms,such as purchase orders or acknowledgements, is for convenience only and all terms and conditions stated thereon are void and of no effect. Should you have any questions concerning this Agreement, please write &quot;product.sales@icesoft.com&quot;;
THE SOFTWARE AND ACCOMPANYING DOCUMENTATION ARE PROTECTED BY UNITED STATES INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY LAW AND INTERNATIONAL TREATY.UNAUTHORIZED REPRODUCTION OR DISTRIBUTION IS SUBJECT TO CIVIL AND CRIMINAL PENALTIES.\n\n\

Eclipse Foundation Software User Agreement\n\
June 06, 2007\n\
\n\
Usage Of Content\n\
THE ECLIPSE FOUNDATION MAKES AVAILABLE SOFTWARE, DOCUMENTATION, INFORMATION AND/OR OTHER MATERIALS FOR OPEN SOURCE PROJECTS (COLLECTIVELY &quot;CONTENT&quot;). USE OF THE CONTENT IS GOVERNED BY THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS AGREEMENT AND/OR THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF LICENSE AGREEMENTS OR NOTICES INDICATED OR REFERENCED BELOW. BY USING THE CONTENT, YOU AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF THE CONTENT IS GOVERNED BY THIS AGREEMENT AND/OR THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF ANY APPLICABLE LICENSE AGREEMENTS OR NOTICES INDICATED OR REFERENCED BELOW. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS AGREEMENT AND THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF ANY APPLICABLE LICENSE AGREEMENTS OR NOTICES INDICATED OR REFERENCED BELOW, THEN YOU MAY NOT USE THE CONTENT.\n\
\n\
Applicable Licenses\n\
Unless otherwise indicated, all Content made available by the Eclipse Foundation is provided to you under the terms and conditions of the Eclipse Public License Version 1.0 (&quot;EPL&quot;). A copy of the EPL is provided with this Content and is also available at http://www.eclipse.org/legal/epl-v10.html. For purposes of the EPL, &quot;Program&quot; will mean the Content.\n\
\n\
Content includes, but is not limited to, source code, object code, documentation and other files maintained in the Eclipse.org CVS repository (&quot;Repository&quot;) in CVS modules (&quot;Modules&quot;) and made available as downloadable archives (&quot;Downloads&quot;).\n\
\n\
Content may be apportioned into plug-ins (&quot;Plug-ins&quot;), plug-in fragments (&quot;Fragments&quot;), and features (&quot;Features&quot;). A Feature is a bundle of one or more Plug-ins and/or Fragments and associated material. Files named &quot;feature.xml&quot; may contain a list of the names and version numbers of the Plug-ins and/or Fragments associated with a Feature. Plug-ins and Fragments are located in directories named &quot;plugins&quot; and Features are located in directories named &quot;features&quot;.\n\
\n\
Features may also include other Features (&quot;Included Features&quot;). Files named &quot;feature.xml&quot; may contain a list of the names and version numbers of Included Features.\n\
\n\
The terms and conditions governing Plug-ins and Fragments should be contained in files named &quot;about.html&quot; (&quot;Abouts&quot;). The terms and conditions governing Features and Included Features should be contained in files named &quot;license.html&quot; (&quot;Feature Licenses&quot;). Abouts and Feature Licenses may be located in any directory of a Download or Module including, but not limited to the following locations:\n\
\n\
The top-level (root) directory\n\
Plug-in and Fragment directories\n\
Subdirectories of the directory named &quot;src&quot; of certain Plug-ins\n\
Feature directories \n\
Note: if a Feature made available by the Eclipse Foundation is installed using the Eclipse Update Manager, you must agree to a license (&quot;Feature Update License&quot;) during the installation process. If the Feature contains Included Features, the Feature Update License should either provide you with the terms and conditions governing the Included Features or inform you where you can locate them. Feature Update Licenses may be found in the &quot;license&quot; property of files named &quot;feature.properties&quot;. Such Abouts, Feature Licenses and Feature Update Licenses contain the terms and conditions (or references to such terms and conditions) that govern your use of the associated Content in that directory.\n\
\n\
THE ABOUTS, FEATURE LICENSES AND FEATURE UPDATE LICENSES MAY REFER TO THE EPL OR OTHER LICENSE AGREEMENTS, NOTICES OR TERMS AND CONDITIONS. SOME OF THESE OTHER LICENSE AGREEMENTS MAY INCLUDE (BUT ARE NOT LIMITED TO):\n\
\n\
Common Public License Version 1.0 (available at http://www.eclipse.org/legal/cpl-v10.html)\n\
Apache Software License 1.1 (available at http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE)\n\
Apache Software License 2.0 (available at http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0)\n\
IBM Public License 1.0 (available at http://oss.software.ibm.com/developerworks/opensource/license10.html)\n\
Metro Link Public License 1.00 (available at http://www.opengroup.org/openmotif/supporters/metrolink/license.html)\n\
Mozilla Public License Version 1.1 (available at http://www.mozilla.org/MPL/MPL-1.1.html)\n\
Common Development and Distribution License (CDDL) Version 1.0 (available at http://www.sun.com/cddl/cddl.html)\n\
IT IS YOUR OBLIGATION TO READ AND ACCEPT ALL SUCH TERMS AND CONDITIONS PRIOR TO USE OF THE CONTENT. If no About, Feature License or Feature Update License is provided, please contact the Eclipse Foundation to determine what terms and conditions govern that particular Content.\n\
\n\
Cryptography\n\
Content may contain encryption software. The country in which you are currently may have restrictions on the import, possession, and use, and/or re-export to another country, of encryption software. BEFORE using any encryption software, please check the country&apos;s laws, regulations and policies concerning the import, possession, or use, and re-export of encryption software, to see if this is permitted.\n
   </license>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.resources" version="3.2.0" match="compatible"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.wst.common.frameworks.ui" version="1.1.0" match="equivalent"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.wst.common.project.facet.ui" version="1.1.0" match="compatible"/>
      <import plugin="com.icesoft.ide.eclipse.icefaces.core" version="3.5.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jst.j2ee.web" version="1.1.0" match="equivalent"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.core" version="3.2.0" match="compatible"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jst.j2ee" version="1.1.0" match="equivalent"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jst.j2ee.core" version="1.1.0" match="equivalent"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jst.common.frameworks" version="1.1.102" match="equivalent"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jst.jsf.core" version="1.1.0" match="compatible"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jst.jsf.facesconfig" version="1.1.1" match="equivalent"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.emf.common" version="2.4.0" match="equivalent"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.emf.ecore" version="2.4.2" match="equivalent"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="com.icesoft.ide.eclipse.icefaces.facelets.core"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="3.5.2.200904081303"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
